# **Daniel Lee Field**

27. Highview Road, Eastergate, Chichester. West Sussex. PO20 3XB (M) 07756-206061 dannyf506@googlemail.com

#### **PROFILE**

A motivated, focussed and personable young mechanical engineer, possessing well developed interpersonal and communication skills that have been demonstrated throughout school, college and working environments in the ability to work on own initiative or as part of an effective team to achieve both corporate and personal goals and targets. An enquiring attitude to new challenges and experiences together with an intuitive approach to problem solving will ensure long term success in both theoretical and practical applications.

#### CAREER HISTORY

**2015 -Present Driver/Driver controller/Warehouse** Euro car parts Chichester branch Employed as part of a dedicated team to supplying automotive parts and equipment to auto repair shops and the general public in West Sussex to the highest standards.

#### **Driver**

Responsible for loading, unloading, preparing, cleaning and operating a vehicle for delivery duties. Transports a wide variety of automotive parts and equipment to different required addresses.

#### **Warehouse Operative**

Responsible for checking damaged or missing items before putting away into stock, moving stock around, picking invoices and keeping the warehouse clean and tidy.

# **Driver Controller**

Responsible for managing a team of delivery drivers, preparing and checking all orders placed through the system. Coordinating the team throughout the day.

- **2012 2014** Environmental Services Clearance Operative Carmarthenshire county council Appointed to join the Cleansing team of Carmarthenshire county council and tasked with the role of ensuring the buildings and lands managed of the county were maintained in good order and kept presentable for all visitors and citizens.
- Ensured that all public areas and facilities were maintained in clean and presentable order at all times, clearing litter and waste from the sites and ensuring disposal in accordance with the county's environmental policy.

#### 2011 – 2012 Pick/Pack Operative

Amazon UK

Employed as part of a dedicated shift team selecting goods for packing and distribution, meeting time critical deadlines as dictated by company.

- Ensured accuracy in order filling, resulting in zero returns due to wrong items being despatched, reducing costs and enhancing Amazon's operation with corporate clients.
- Packed items for distribution, ensuring goods were properly and securely protected during transit.

**2010 – 2011** Environmental Services Clearance Operative Gwilli Steam Railway Appointed to join the services team of the steam railway and tasked with the role of ensuring the buildings and lands managed by the trust were maintained in good order and kept presentable for all visitors.

- ♦ Ensured that all public areas and facilities were maintained in clean and presentable order at all times, clearing litter and waste from the sites and ensuring disposal in accordance with the railways environmental policy.
- ♦ Assisted in the maintenance of buildings ensuring that all areas were a8t all times fit and safe for staff and public use.
- Undertook cleaning of carriages and ensured that footplate's of locomotives open to public were kept in good order and clear of obstructions ensuring maximum levels of public safety at all times.

# **2009 – 2010** Sales Assistant

Easy Legal Services

Appointed to assist in the sale and provision of legal services to members of the public seeking compensation for injury or loss.

- Responded to incoming phone calls from the public, explaining the services of the company and providing information regarding claim handling and management to potential clients.
- ♦ Completed initial paperwork for submission to legal team and sent out prepared client sales agreements to ensure new clients were able to start issue resolution as speedily as possible.

**2008 – 2009 Trainee Mechanical Engineer work experience** Carmarthenshire County Council. Appointed to role of trainee mechanical engineer within the councils transport department assisting in the maintenance of all the vehicles and mechanical equipments used by the organisation.

2007 – 2008 Motor Work Shop, General Assistant Touts Garage

**2006 – 2006 Electricians Assistant work experience** Evans Electrical Services

# **EDUCATION**

**2006 – 2007 Swansea College** City and Guilds Level 2 Certificate in Maintenance and Repair – Light Vehicles

**2005 – 2006 Chichester College** City and Guilds Level 1 Key Skills in Communication Entry Level 3 Award in Automotive Vehicle Maintenance

Lantra Awards:

Chainsaw, Cross-cutting and Maintenance Licence Ride-on Lawnmower and Maintenance Licence Petrol brush cutter and Maintenance Licence 2000 – 2005 St Phillip Howard High School

#### **KEY SKILLS**

Well developed telephone communication skills

Numerate and Literate.

Sound level of understanding regarding Information and Communication Technology

Health and Safety in the workplace.

Personal Railway Track Safety

# **PERSONAL**

**Age:** 28 years **Date of Birth:** 25 April 1989

**Status:** Single 1 dependents Full Clean UK Driving Licence since 2007

# **INTERESTS**

Family, Fitness, Information technology, Using computers to edit videos, photos and to extend personal knowledge, Coast Steering, Camping, Mountain Biking, Motor Vehicles and mechanical equipment. International Travel to experience different cultures.